<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our work on DCUBED | Dream. Design. Develop | Brisbane Web Design</title>
    <link>https://dcubed.com.au/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our work on DCUBED | Dream. Design. Develop | Brisbane Web Design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 22:54:14 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dcubed.com.au/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hipcharts Mobile App</title>
      <link>https://dcubed.com.au/work/hipcharts-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 22:54:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dcubed.com.au/work/hipcharts-case-study/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s your top 5? Are you one of those people who are just so passionate about their music that they feel they need to document their favourite tracks by an artist and let everyone know about it? Well Hipcharts aims to give you that power by allowing you to create your own charts of your top 5 favourite songs by any artist.
                                                                       Powered by Spotify Spotify not only has one of the largest collections of music metadata but it opens up personalisation within an app when used for authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beachside Bargains Landing Page</title>
      <link>https://dcubed.com.au/work/beachside-bargains-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 22:54:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dcubed.com.au/work/beachside-bargains-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Beachside vibes for Beachside Bargains Beachside Bargains already had a good looking logo to work with that allowed us to seamlessly integrate a beachy vibe with bold and vibrant colours. As you scroll on both mobile and desktop it transitions the sky from a sunny blue horizon into a beautiful orange sunset, while the logo sets in the background. Gorgeous!
With it&amp;rsquo;s mobile-first design, the call to actions are positioned perfectly near those eager thumbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance X Sales Page</title>
      <link>https://dcubed.com.au/work/finx-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dcubed.com.au/work/finx-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Requirements FinX is a finance solutions company that offers financial services to customers looking to purchase vehicles, equipment, marine, caravans and other commercial goods.
At the time FinX did not have a website to direct potential customers to and therefor needed one built, asap.
The primary goal of this new website will be to generate leads as well as provide an online presence.
Responsive website The new landing page is a ‘responsive’ website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grow2 Web Application</title>
      <link>https://dcubed.com.au/work/grow2-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dcubed.com.au/work/grow2-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Grow2 required a suite of applications to run on desktop and mobile for both adminstrators (content creators) and the people receiving the material.
The point was made early on by the team at Grow2 that everybody had to have the ability to learn in their preferred way. Some people preferred reading content, some prefer a video, others enjoy listening to audio. This meant we would need to take advantage of cloud hosting using Amazon AWS S3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>