<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on DCUBED | Dream. Design. Develop | Brisbane Web Design</title>
    <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on DCUBED | Dream. Design. Develop | Brisbane Web Design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dcubed.com.au/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create smoother animations with animation-fill-mode</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/smoother-css-animations-with-fill-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/smoother-css-animations-with-fill-mode/</guid>
      <description>What is animation-fill-mode? animation-fill-mode is a CSS property which tells an animation how to apply styles to the target element before or after it is run.
In this post we will be focussing on the use of the value animation-fill-mode: forwards, This value allows the target element to maintain the styles applied in the final keyframes of it&amp;rsquo;s animation.
Why is this so good? When you use animation-fill-mode: forward you can set the initial styles of elements to be hidden or offscreen and then use the styles in your keysframes to determine the final state of your UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a prototype app using production data</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/prototyping-with-real-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/prototyping-with-real-data/</guid>
      <description>What is production data? Production data is data that is either a clone or the direct source of data that is used to power your exisiting apps. Typically your apps will receive data from &amp;ldquo;endpoints&amp;rdquo; which have been designed to return particular data. For example, your currenty app may call yourapp.com/api/countries to get a list of Countries.
The key here is the connection the content being used to compose a designers mock and what we will end up showing to our users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance X - Case Study</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/finx-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/finx-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Requirements FinX is a finance solutions company that offers financial services to customers looking to purchase vehicles, equipment, marine, caravans and other commercial goods.
At the time FinX did not have a website to direct potential customers to and therefor needed one built, asap.
The primary goal of this new website will be to generate leads as well as provide an online presence.
Responsive website The new landing page is a ‘responsive’ website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grow2 - Case Study</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/grow2-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/grow2-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Grow2 required a suite of applications to run on desktop and mobile for both adminstrators (content creators) and the people receiving the material.
The point was made early on by the team at Grow2 that everybody had to have the ability to learn in their preferred way. Some people preferred reading content, some prefer a video, others enjoy listening to audio. This meant we would need to take advantage of cloud hosting using Amazon AWS S3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple way to A/B test your Vue prototypes</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/simple-ab-test-in-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/simple-ab-test-in-prototypes/</guid>
      <description>Remote testing is an easy way to scale up your user testing. There are many great tools out there to help facilitate these kind of sessions.
Sometimes though you may be in two minds about which design you want to test and you only have the ability to provide a single URL for the user to access. Luckily we can use a little javascript to allow our browsers to randomly decide which design we want to show our user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uploading files direct to S3 using Vue, Dropzone &amp; NodeJS</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/uploading-direct-to-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/uploading-direct-to-s3/</guid>
      <description>Encountering this issue in a project recently, in which we use vue-dropzone, a Vue.js component for DropzoneJS which appears to provide upload directly to AWS S3 functionality out of the box.
Looking at the documentation, it appears that we need a URL signer to return an S3 Policy in the following format:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14  { &amp;#34;signature&amp;#34;:{ &amp;#34;Content-Type&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;acl&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;public-read-write&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;success_action_status&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;201&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;policy&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;abc123&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;X-amz-credential&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;AKIAIM3WELV3PLALOYDQ\/20171012\/us-west-2\/s3\/aws4_request&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;X-amz-algorithm&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;X-amz-date&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;20171012T054729Z&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;X-amz-signature&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;5227d84360d92ef8al45549805b3746f2f1d6641df8986aamcr939c35513cd7c&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;key&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;&amp;#34; }, &amp;#34;postEndpoint&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;\/\/s3-us-west-2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>