<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Best App Developers in Brisbane | DCUBED - Dream Design Develop</title>
    <link>http://dcubed.com.au/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Best App Developers in Brisbane | DCUBED - Dream Design Develop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 16:31:02 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dcubed.com.au/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/services/web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 16:31:02 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/services/web-development/</guid>
      <description>Large scale websites If your business needs a website that needs to do a little more heavy lifting than just a simple Wordpress site with a simple contact form and an image gallery then you’ve come to the right place. Our team has years of experience creating and maintaining robust websites that handle millions of requests a day. We specialise in creating websites that take advantage of more advanced features such as - multi-level account systems, email notifications, Stripe integration and payment gateways, file upload which take advantage of Amazon Web Services such as S3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Strategy and User Experience</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/services/strategy-and-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/services/strategy-and-ux/</guid>
      <description>Design at DCUBED is done very different to how things typically play out at other agencies. We have figured out over the years that the quicker we learn about a design, the more success we have with it. And there is no way faster way to get your hands on a design than through code.
Our proficiency with CSS and other front end languages means that once we move past a &amp;ldquo;white board sesh&amp;rdquo;, we&amp;rsquo;re ready to start bringing our ideas to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/services/seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/services/seo/</guid>
      <description>Design Sprints App design If you have your own development team and just need someone who can help you untangle your thoughts and visually bring them to life, we can also help with this. Fortunately, we speak the same language developers do, so we can make sure that we create achievable designs and work with your team to execute. We can deliver design assets in any format that suits you needs, PDF, Sketch files or via design platform tools like inVision.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>