<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Best App Developers in Brisbane | DCUBED - Dream Design Develop</title>
    <link>http://dcubed.com.au/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Best App Developers in Brisbane | DCUBED - Dream Design Develop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 16:31:02 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dcubed.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/services/web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 16:31:02 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/services/web-development/</guid>
      <description>Large scale websites If your business needs a website that needs to do a little more heavy lifting than just a simple Wordpress site with a simple contact form and an image gallery then you’ve come to the right place. Our team has years of experience creating and maintaining robust websites that handle millions of requests a day. We specialise in creating websites that take advantage of more advanced features such as - multi-level account systems, email notifications, Stripe integration and payment gateways, file upload which take advantage of Amazon Web Services such as S3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Strategy and User Experience</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/services/strategy-and-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/services/strategy-and-ux/</guid>
      <description>Design Sprints DCUBED can facilitate or train teams on how to run design sprints is a five day process for validating ideas and solving big challenges through prototyping and testing ideas with customer
App design If you have your own development team and just need someone who can help you untangle your thoughts and visually bring them to life, we can also help with this.Fortunately, we speak the same language developers do, so we can make sure that we create achievable designs and work with your team to execute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/services/seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 16:30:14 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/services/seo/</guid>
      <description>Design Sprints App design If you have your own development team and just need someone who can help you untangle your thoughts and visually bring them to life, we can also help with this. Fortunately, we speak the same language developers do, so we can make sure that we create achievable designs and work with your team to execute. We can deliver design assets in any format that suits you needs, PDF, Sketch files or via design platform tools like inVision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create smoother animations with animation-fill-mode</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/smoother-css-animations-with-fill-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/smoother-css-animations-with-fill-mode/</guid>
      <description>What is animation-fill-mode? animation-fill-mode is a CSS property which tells an animation how to apply styles to the target element before or after it is run.
In this post we will be focussing on the use of the value animation-fill-mode: forwards, This value allows the target element to maintain the styles applied in the final keyframes of it&amp;rsquo;s animation.
Why is this so good? When you use animation-fill-mode: forward you can set the initial styles of elements to be hidden or offscreen and then use the styles in your keysframes to determine the final state of your UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating fool proof prototypes with production data</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/prototyping-with-real-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/prototyping-with-real-data/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finance X - Case Study</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/finx-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/finx-case-study/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grow2 - Case Study</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/grow2-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/grow2-case-study/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple way to A/B test in your prototypes</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/simple-ab-test-in-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/simple-ab-test-in-prototypes/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When to use animate or transition in CSS</title>
      <link>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/when-to-animate-vs-transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dcubed.com.au/blog/when-to-animate-vs-transition/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>